

## **Contacts**

Phone: +48 531 310 527 E-mail: witold.g83@gmail.com

# Technical Skills

- HTML
- CSS
- SQL
- · C++
- InTouch
- Linux
- Python

## **Soft Skills**

- Responsibility
- Easy contact with people
- Quick learning ability
- Teamwork

DOWNLOAD CV

# Witold Grzesiak

#### Engineer

I am a graduate of the University of Zielona Góra, specializing in Industrial Automation. I am also a master's student in Computer Science at the same university. I'm passionate about new technologies and the use of AI in medicine

## **Achievements**

- 1. Social assistant to MP Anita Kucharska-Dziedzic
- 2. <u>Canva Course Online graphics from scratch</u>
- 3. Linux Course for beginners

## **Employment History**

Junior Remote Service Support Specialist at Ekoenergetyka - Service

August 2023 – December 2024

- Remote diagnosis of charging stations
- Remote repair of electric chargers
- Support for service partners, customers, and technicians
- Remote software updates

#### **Junior Specialist in Emergency Service**

February 2023 – August 2023

- Repairing electric chargers
- Installing chargers
- Performing periodic inspections
- Diagnosing chargers

#### **Service Assistant**

July 2022 - February 2023

- Repairing electric chargers
- Installing chargers
- Performing periodic inspections

# Hospitality Leader at FMD Jadwiga Wieczorek – McDonald's

June 2019 - May 2020

- Providing guests with information about the restaurant's current offers
- Maintaining cleanliness in the lobby
- Managing the cleaning team

## **Education**

Computer Science, University of Zielona Góra

February 2023 – Present

**Automation and Robotics, University of Zielona Góra** 

October 2019 – February 2023